<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safal Store</string>
    <string name="app_actionbar_name"><u>SAFAL</u></string>
    <string name="safal_intro">
        Safal is engaged in retailing of fresh fruits and vegetables and value added products
        fruit juices, ketchup, pickles, jams, frozen peas and tomato puree. Of late, Safal introduced un-polished pulses
        under its own brand. Other products like Mother Dairy’s desi ghee, ice creams, lassi, chhach, mishti doi, paneer
        and Dhara’s oil range are also available at Safal retail outlets.
        \nSafal is the largest retail chain of fresh fruits and vegetables in Delhi. At present we are operating about 400
        retail outlets in Delhi, Noida, Ghaziabad, Faridabad, Gurgaon and 23 retail outlets in Bangalore which cater to
        more than 1.5 lakh customers per day. We provide around 120 SKUs of fresh fruits and vegetables.
        Our retail shops are primarily operated by ex-servicemen or their dependents.
    </string>
    <string name="frozen_green_peas">
        Safal Green Peas are Frozen by IQF Technique(Individual Quick Freezing) through a freezing tunnel of fluidized bed,
        leading to freezing of each and every pea grain individually. In this process, cells do not rupture/damage,
        preserving the natural nutrition and flavour of the peas. Safal green peas are natural and free from added preservatives
        or additives.
        \nWhat’s special about Safal Frozen Range?
        \n- Processed by IQF techniques to preserve the natural nutrition and flavour of the green peas 
        \n- Year round availability
        \nShelf Life - 12 Months
        \nPack Size - 200 g, 500g, 1 Kg and 5 Kg
    </string>

    <string name="safal_mixed_vegitable">
        Safal frozen mixed vegetables are hygienically cleaned and completely natural, keeping them as fresher as
        vegetables found in local markets. The products gets frozen by using IQF techniques (individual Quick freezing)
        technique, through a freezing tunnel of fluidized bed, leading to freezing Of each and every grain individually.
        \nIn this process cells do not rupture/damage, hence preserving the natural nutrition and flavour.
        \nShelf Life   -  12 Months
        \nPack Size   -   200 g and 500 g
    </string>

    <string name="safal_jackfruit">
        What is Safal Frozen Jackfruit?
        \nWe all love to eat Jackfruit but hate the hassle that comes with it Safal frozen Jackfruit is tender,
        sweet and carefully handpicked. The unique freezing process locks its freshness and retains the nutrition.
        \nJust cut open a pack today and say goodbye to sticky hands.
        \nShelf life    -  12 Months
        \nPack Size   -  300 g
    </string>

    <string name="safal_frozen_corn">
        Safal frozen corn is hygienically cleaned and completely natural, keeping them as fresher as fresh corn found
        in local markets. The corn kernels gets frozen using IQF (Individual Quick Freezing) technique , through a freezing
        tunnel of fluidized bed, leading to freezing of each kernel individually. In this process cells do not rupture/damage,
        hence preserving the nutrition and flavor.
        \nShelf Life  -  12 Months
        \nPack Size  -  200 g, 500 g and 1 Kg
    </string>

    <string name="safal_aloo_tikki">
        Made from the choicest of potatoes from the best of farms, Safal Aloo Tikki Brings you freshness and taste 
        like never before. An all time favourite snack for all age groups, it will brighten up any party and make a 
        perfect picnic snack too.
        \nWhat’s special about Safal Frozen Range?
        \n- Traditional Indian easy to cook
        \n- Hygienic Preparation untouched by hand
        \n- Doesn’t Break/ Crack on Frying
        \n- Consistent and Quality
    </string>

    <string name="safal_hara_kebab">
        Made from the choicest potatoes from the best of Farms, Safal Hara Bhara Kebab brings you never before
        Freshness and taste. Open the pack, fry them and within minutes these crispy and delicious Safal Hara Bhara
        Kebab are ready to be served. Be it your children or guests Safal Hara Bhara Kebab are always a delicious favourite.
    </string>

    <string name="safal_tomato">
        Good thing comes in small packages’ – a perfect description for 200 g pack Safal tomato puree.
        Made from choicest of tomatoes from the finest of farms, Safal tomato puree brings you the nature’s goodness
        like never before to liven up your curries, soups, gravies, pizza dressings, etc. with no added color flavor or
        preservatives, it gives you same taste and feeling of natural tomatoes without putting the efforts in handpicking and
        fine chopping the same.
        \nWhat’s Special about Safal product?
        \n- Made from Fresh Chosen Red Tomatoes from farm
        \nShelf Life  -  12 Months
        \nPack Size  -  200 g
    </string>

    <string name="safal_pulses">
        Introduce yourself to healthy food with the all new range of Safal unpolished pulses, which are free from 
        any artificial color and adulteration. Unpolished pulses are pure pulses which are healthier and tastier 
        and rich in natural protein.
        \nWhat’s Special about Safal pulses?
        \n- Unpolished
        \n- Two stage cleaning
        \n- Hygienically sorted and graded to maintain purity
        \nShelf Life - 6 Months
        \nPack Size - 500 g and 1 Kg
    </string>

    <string name="safal_fruits">
        Safal Fal. Surakshit Fal.
        \nFruits are nature’s wonderful medicines packed with vitamins, minerals, anti-oxidants. They are absolute feast
        to our sight, not just because of their color and flavor but also help in keeping body fit and healthy!
    </string>

    <string name="safal_veg">
        Safal Fresh Vegetables
        \nThe entire procurement network is spread over 20 states including North East, comprising nearly 8000
        farmer members from 93 Safal growers associations.
    </string>

    <string name="safal_honey">
        Extracted From Naturally sealed honey combs, Safal Honey is 100% natural.
        Naturally Sealed honey combs are filled with honey and then sealed by bees themselves. The honey is extracted by the
        professionals to give you the taste of pure and 100% natural honey 
        \nWhat’s Special….
        \nExtracted by experts from Naturally sealed honey combs Qualifies FSSAI, CODEX, European
        Union Standard for its Quality and Composition
        \nShelf Life - 12 Months
        \nPack Size - 250 g and 500 g
    </string>

    <string name="safal_onion">
        Safal Easy Onions or dehydrated onions offered by us are obtained by drying or dehydrating red onions.
        Easy Onions are used in preparations of soups, sauces, food preparations, vegetable, stuffing mixes, fast foods etc. 
        Non-fried, dehydrated onion flakes that enhances your cooking experience while keeping the taste of freshly chopped
        onions intact.
        \nLess effort of cutting, chopping, etc.
        \nNo tears in eyes
        \nLess time
        \nUses Less Oil
        \nEasy to store
        \nConsistent quality
        \nFree from price fluctuations
        \n30 grams = 300 grams of fresh onions
        \nShelf Life  -  12 Months
        \nPack Size -  30 g and 120 g
    </string>

    <string name="safal_besan">
        Freshly ground, Safal Besan is processed from pure and best quality of chana. It is used to pan out delicious
        Halwas and many savouries and snacks.
        \nShelf Life  - 3 Months
        \nPack Size - 500 g and 1 Kg
    </string>
    <string name="logo_name">it is logo</string>
    <string name="safal_pic">it is safal pic</string>

</resources>
